astraware.com 2003-06-07

# Astraware: Privacy Policy

**Note:** Your browser doesn't appear to support the latest web browser standards such as CSS, meaning that our site may not display correctly. We recommend [Internet Explorer 6](http://www.microsoft.com/ie), [Netscape 7](http://www.netscape.com/download), [Opera 7](http://www.opera.com/) or [Mozilla 1.3](http://www.mozilla.org/) or later. If you don't think this applies to your web browser, contact [Webmaster](mailto:webmaster@astraware.com), quoting 'ia_archiver'.

### Astraware Privacy Policy

**What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?**

Visitors may supply personally identifiable information (such as name, address or telephone numbers) for various purposes on this site. These purposes include registering for our software, requesting further information about our products, asking for support or a asking question about Astraware. Astraware does not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. This means that you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself.

**How is it used?**

When you register for our software, we will add your details to our mailing list for sending out product updates and newsletters telling you about our products. When you supply information about yourself for any other specific purpose, we use the information for only that purpose (such as to provide the information you have requested), unless you agree or indicate otherwise. 

**Security**

Personally identifiable information is stored on our server and is not publicly accessible. Further, personally identifiable information is only accessed by Astraware employees on a "need to know" basis. 

**Opt-out**

If you have registered to receive e-mail communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distribution lists. You can do this by contacting [registrations@astraware.com](mailto:registrations@astraware.com). 

**Correct/Update**

If you would like to verify the data we have received from you or to make corrections to it, you may contact us directly at the e-mail address provided above.

**Links**

This site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

**E-mail Links**

We use e-mail links located on this site to allow you to contact us directly via e-mail. We use the information provided in your e-mail to respond to your questions or comments. We may also store your comments for future reference. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your permission.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Astraware.

**For more information**

If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please e-mail [privacy@astraware.com](mailto:privacy@astraware.com).
